{
  "rounds": [
    {
      "round_name": "The Mommy",
      "question": "How many children did the fifth most fertile woman have in her lifetime?",
      "solution": "52",
      "answer": "Maddalena Granata - Maddalena Granata (born 1839) Nocera, Italy, who married at 28, had given birth to 52 living and dead children, 49 being males, by 1886. Dr. de Sanctis, of Nocera, stated that she had 15 sets of triplets."
    },
    {
      "round_name": "The Mommy",
      "question": "Breast milk is deficient in Iron and .....",
      "solution": "Vitamin D",
      "answer": "WTE - https://www.whattoexpect.com/first-year/feeding-your-baby/vitamins-and-babies.aspx"
    },
    {
      "round_name": "The Mommy",
      "question": "As per NIH, there are 3 stages of labor: Early & active labor, Delivery of the baby, Delivery of the ....._",
      "solution": "placenta",
      "answer": "NIH."
    },
    {
      "round_name": "The Mommy",
      "question": "The Bishop Score is the most commonly used method to rate the readiness of the ......",
      "solution": "cervix",
      "answer": "NCBI - www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov"
    },
    {
      "round_name": "The Mommy",
      "question": "Starting around week 35, moms-to-be have an increased urge to ....._",
      "solution": "pee",
      "answer": "NIH."
    },
    {
      "round_name": "The Mommy",
      "question": "Lactation consultants often call it 'liquid gold', but there's a scientific name for golden, creamy pre-milk that comes before breast milk is secreted. What's the name?",
      "solution": "Colostrum",
      "answer": "from nuggets of wisdom"
    },
    {
      "round_name": "The Baby",
      "question": "What is the one flavor that newborn's tastebuds cannot taste?",
      "solution": "Salt",
      "answer": "Tastebuds for salt develops at around 4-6 months of age."
    },
    {
      "round_name": "The Baby",
      "question": "Lanugo is very thin, soft, usually unpigmented, downy ..... that is sometimes found on the body of a fetal or new-born human.",
      "solution": "hair",
      "answer": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lanugo"
    },
    {
      "round_name": "The Baby",
      "question": "Witch's ....., that is secreted in around 5% of newborns, is considered a normal physiological occurrence and no treatment or testing is necessary.",
      "solution": "milk",
      "answer": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Witch%27s_milk"
    },
    {
      "round_name": "The Baby",
      "question": "On an average, how many hours of sleep do parents get in a night for the first year?",
      "solution": "5",
      "answer": "According to healthline.com"
    }
  ]
}
